<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Weather Woo Kotlin</string>
    <string name="forecast_icon">Forcast Icon</string>
    
    <string name="text2">
        From other countries:\n
        View Phone numbers for the United Customer Contact Center.
    </string>

    <string name="title_2">
        Wheelchair equipment supplied by United

        Airport wheelchairs

        We have wheelchairs available for customers with disabilities to use at each
        of our airports. it\'s best to request a wheelchair in advance before the day of travel
        trough your travel agent or the United Accessibility Desk at 1-800-228-2744 within the U.S
        or Canada. If you\'re calling from elsewhere, please call the United Customer Contact Center
        and ask to be connected to the Accessibility Desk. Upon arrival at the airport notify a United
        representative or skycap (if skycap service is available at that airport) that you require
        a wheelchair for transportation to the departure gate. The usual width of these wheelchairs
        is 18 inches (45.7 cm). For your convenience, the following airports have assistance centers
        in their lobbies, which are located near:\n
        \u25CF DEN - Terminal West, Level 6, between Doors 614-616\n
        \u25CF EWR - Terminal C, Level 2, Door 4\n
        \u25CF LAD - Main Terminal, Door 4B\n
        \u25CF LAX - Terminal 7, Door L2-10\n
        \u25CF ORD - Terminal 1, Door 1G\n
        \u25CF SFO - Terminal 3, Door 11\n

        Aisle wheelchairs

        We also offer aisle wheelchairs for transferring non-ambulatory customers to and from their
        seats on the aircraft.

        Onboard wheelchairs
        Every aircraft with more than 60 seats has an onboard wheelchair. These wheelchairs are
        specially designed to fit the aisle of our aircraft and may be used to access tha lavatory.
        Our inflight personnel are trained in the use of this wheelchair and will assist you.


    </string>
</resources>
